[{"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 1}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 1}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 2}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 2}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 3}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 3}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 4}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 4}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}]}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "mean-num", "title": "选一选", "stem": "哪个可以用", "num": "0", "stem2": "表示？", "list": [{"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 0}, {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}]}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "level": "1", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-8-03"}]